OKX has launched X1, a ZK-powered layer 2 network that connects the OKX and Ethereum communities to allow anyone to take part in a truly global on-chain ecosystem. During this event, you have an opportunity to build on the X1 testnet and build with the latest Account Abstraction technologies. Happy hacking!
Prizes
▼
⚡ Most novel dApp on X1 ⸺ $4,500

   ① $3,000       ② $1,500   
For this prize, we are looking for the most original dApps deployed to our new X1 chain. X1 is a new, cutting-edge zero-knowledge L2 network powered by OKX and built with the Polygon CDK. Whether you are a new developer or Web3 wizard, we invite you to bring your creativity to the most global community of builders.
Qualification Requirements
Your dApp must be deployed or connected to X1. The submission should be an open source project with clear documentation. And finally, this must be a project that is newly developed to ensure fairness.
Links and Resources
X1 Documentation
https://www.okx.com/x1/docs/developer/build-on-x1/quickstart
↗
▼
🪄 Best use of Account Abstraction ⸺ $500
Account Abstraction is the hottest new thing in Web3! Show us what you got by deploying a dApp with our integrated smart wallet account or create new tool to help other developers create AA applications.
Qualification Requirements
Your dApp must be deployed or connected to X1. The submission should be an open source project with clear documentation. And finally, this must be a project that is newly developed to ensure fairness.
Resources
OKX India Twitter
https://twitter.com/okxindia
↗
OKX India Community
https://discord.com/invite/5Pk84Pd2S3
↗
Web3 Developer Docs
https://www.okx.com/web3/build/docs/home/welcome
↗

