About
Polygon is the leading platform for Ethereum scaling and infrastructure development. Its growing suite of products offers developers easy access to all major scaling and infrastructure solutions: L2 solutions (ZK Rollups and Optimistic Rollups), sidechains, hybrid solutions, stand-alone and enterprise chains, data availability solutions, and more. Polygon's scaling solutions have seen widespread adoption with 18000+ applications hosted, 1B+ total transactions processed, ~100M+ unique user addresses, and $5B+ in assets secured.
Prizes
▼
🏆 Best use of zkEVM ⸺ $5,000

Up to 4 teams will receive $1,250
The Polygon zkEVM launched earlier this year and it has grown to hold a TVL of $50 million and continues to attract major protocols. For this challenge, we want to see your most innovative use of the Polygon zkEVM, this is an open challenge that will see the most innovative and deserving protocols with killer UX carry the day!
Qualification Requirements
Be Innovative
Deploy to the zkEVM
Note: You can deploy to Mumbai if you're project requires another service provider that's not supported on the Polygon zkEVM
Links and Resources
Documentation
https://wiki.polygon.technology/docs/zkevm/
↗
Full Stack Demo
https://github.com/teeolendo/climatecoin/
↗
The ULTIMATE Developers Guide To Polygon zkEVM
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pkvgS26VR8E
↗
▼
📈 Polygon zkEVM DeFi Challenge ⸺ $5,000

Up to 4 teams will receive $1,250
With the launch of the Polygon zkEVM, brand new rails were established that allow DeFi developers to get started with deploying on L2s. In this challenge, we are inviting participants to deploy a General DeFi application of any category to the Polygon zkEVM Testnet.
Qualification Requirements
The requirements are dead simple:
- Develop a DeFi application.
- Deploy the application on Polygon zkEVM Testnet / Mainnet
- Integrate an OpenZeppelin library
▼
🔨 Use a Polygon Tool ⸺ $4,000

Up to 4 teams will receive $1,000
We know that building a dApp that queries blockchain data can be cumbersome. With the Chain Indexer Framework you can unlock the true potential of EVM blockchains by seamlessly integrating them into your data infrastructure. Whether you are building real-time analytics, decentralised applications, or any other data-driven solution, this framework assists you in developing robust and efficient event-driven data pipelines on EVM blockchains.
Some Sample Use-Cases:
- Wallet Services: Blockchain indexers can help wallet providers offer more features like transaction history, balance history, and real-time updates.
- dApp Backend: dApps often require real-time access to contract events, token transactions, and other on-chain activities. A data indexer can speed up this process considerably.
- Analytics and Monitoring: Firms specialising in blockchain analytics use indexers to monitor activities like fraudulent transactions, smart contract interactions, and trends in token transfers.
- Cross-Chain Services: For cross-chain swaps or interactions, indexers can offer data that facilitates more seamless integrations.
- Oracles: Data indexers can support oracles by providing them with a more efficient way to access specific data points on the blockchain.
- NFT Marketplaces: To track ownership changes, price histories, and various attributes of NFTs, data indexers are often used in the backend.
Qualification Requirements
Deploy the Chain Indexer Framework and integrate it to a smart contract on Polygon zkEVM and provide links to your deployment and your deployed smart contract addresses.
Links and Resources
Npm install @maticnetwork/chain-indexer-framework
https://github.com/0xPolygon/chain-indexer-framework
↗
Github
https://github.com/0xPolygon/chain-indexer-framework
↗
Wiki
https://wiki.polygon.technology/docs/tools/chain-indexer-framework/overview/
↗
Blog
https://blog.jarrodwatts.com/create-a-blockchain-indexer-with-chain-indexer-framework
↗
▼
🏗️ dApp Launchpad ⸺ $1,000

Up to 2 teams will receive $500
The dApp Launchpad is a dApp and smart contract development tool tailored for the Polygon blockchain networks. It provides a set of required tools and templates for accelerating and / or enhancing the development of their unique decentralised applications designed on the Polygon ecosystem. This scaffold aims to streamline the process for developers, particularly those new to the web3 space, allowing them to quickly start, understand, and modify code for their projects.
Functionalities are offered in a CLI tool to quickly initialise a fully-integrated Polygon dApp, create a development environment, and deploy everything to production.
Run `npm install: @0xpolygon/polygon-dapp-scaffold`
Qualification Requirements
Build a dApp using the dapp Scaffold tool and deploy to a provider of your choice.
Provide a link to your repo and to your deployed dApp
Links and Resources
Github
https://github.com/0xPolygon/dapp-launchpad
↗
▼
🆔 Best use of Polygon ID to preserve user privacy ⸺ $5,000

Up to 4 teams will receive $1,250
Self-Sovereign Identity is the future. Use Polygon ID to represent identity-based information as verifiable credentials in your dapp so your users can prove access rights to dapp features without giving up their private data. Polygon ID is also excited to announce a brand new partnership with Dock.io that will allow you to securely extend the privacy of your Lens profile using Verifiable Credentials. Using Dock's REST API credentials can be issued in a few API calls. Along with issuing credentials application developers can use the API to manage issuer profiles and create and import data schemas.
Dock's tooling also supports non-developers through it's no-code solution Dock Certs which provides the same functionality via a web interface.
Qualification Requirements
Build a full stack dApp that utilizes Polygon ID to issue decentralized identifiers and verifiable credentials. Your application should cover the full lifecycle of verifiable credentials, issuance, holding using the Polygon ID wallet and verification from your dApp.
Links and Resources
Polygon ID Documentation
https://devs.polygonid.com/
↗
VC Gated Full Stack Dapp
https://github.com/oceans404/fullstack-polygon-id-vc-gated-dapp/tree/main
↗
Dock.io Demo App
https://github.com/docknetwork/polygonid-demo
↗
How to set up a Issuer Node
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=19E-jLLRUO8&feature=youtu.be
↗

