About
Push Protocol is the communication protocol of web3. Push protocol enables cross-chain notifications and messaging for dapps, wallets, and services tied to wallet addresses in an open, gasless, and platform-agnostic fashion. The open communication layer allows any crypto wallet / frontend to tap into the network and get the communication across.
Prizes
▼
🔔 Best Use of Push Protocol ⸺ $8,000

   ① $2,500       ② $2,500       ③ $1,500       ④ $1,500   
𝟭. 𝗖𝗿𝗲𝗮𝘁𝗶𝘃𝗲 𝗕𝗼𝘂𝗻𝘁𝘆
We seek the most ingenious solutions built using the Push Protocol. Challenge the norms and serve up your most creative implementations.
𝟮. 𝗣𝘂𝘀𝗵 𝗖𝗵𝗮𝘁 𝗖𝗼𝗻𝗱𝗶𝘁𝗶𝗼𝗻𝗮𝗹 𝗚𝗮𝘁𝗶𝗻𝗴 𝗜𝗻𝘁𝗲𝗴𝗿𝗮𝘁𝗶𝗼𝗻 𝗳𝗼𝗿 𝗗𝗔𝗽𝗽𝘀
Showcase the potential of the Push by integrating its Conditional Gating feature into their dapps. This feature will allow dapps to create dynamic and sophisticated permissions for their user community, setting unique conditions for joining or communicating in groups.
𝟯. 𝗡𝗼𝘁𝗶𝗳𝗶𝗰𝗮𝘁𝗶𝗼𝗻/𝗖𝗵𝗮𝗻𝗻𝗲𝗹 𝘀𝗲𝘁𝘁𝗶𝗻𝗴𝘀 𝗜𝗺𝗽𝗹𝗲𝗺𝗲𝗻𝘁𝗮𝘁𝗶𝗼𝗻
Illustrate the power of Push Notifications by incorporating its Notification Settings option into your dapp. This feature allows users to tailor the notifications they receive, thereby ensuring a more personalized user experience. With Boolean and Slider Settings as part of the Notification Settings, users gain the flexibility to switch preferences on and off and fine-tune them, increasing the customization and relevance of each notification.
𝟰. 𝗕𝗲𝘀𝘁 𝘂𝘀𝗲 𝗼𝗳 𝗣𝘂𝘀𝗵 𝗽𝗿𝗼𝘁𝗼𝗰𝗼𝗹
This bounty recognizes the most exceptional and impactful implementation of the Push Protocol, emphasizing applications that significantly enhance user interaction and experience through effective use of Push features.
Links and Resources
Channel Settings
https://push.org/docs/notifications/build/create-channel-settings/
↗
Conditional gating
https://push.org/docs/chat/build/conditional-rules-for-group/
↗
Stream Notifications
https://push.org/docs/notifications/build/stream-notifications/
↗
Push Documentation
https://push.org/docs/
↗
▼
🙏🏽 Namaste Push Protocol Bounty ⸺ $2,000
We started with GM GM and now today we are here with Namaste, but it all started with social initiative. So, this bounty is dedicated to best use of Push Protocol in Social based Dapps. Whether to use Notifications for all the important alerts, or move even further with Notification settings to customize notifs, and no dapp is complete without chat functionality, and over this push provides super power of conditional gating too.𝗘𝘅𝗮𝗺𝗽𝗹𝗲𝘀 𝗳𝗼𝗿 𝗜𝗻𝘀𝗽𝗶𝗿𝗮𝘁𝗶𝗼𝗻: 𝟭. 𝗦𝗼𝗰𝗶𝗮𝗹𝗜𝗺𝗽𝗮𝗰𝘁𝗛𝘂𝗯 : A DApp dedicated to social activists, where users can receive notifications about upcoming rallies or events. Using conditional gating, activists with specific badges or tokens can access private planning rooms. 𝟮. 𝗘𝗰𝗼𝗔𝗹𝗲𝗿𝘁 : An environmental initiative platform where users can chat about sustainable practices and get notified about eco-friendly events or sudden environmental crises. 𝟯. 𝗖𝗼𝗺𝗺𝘂𝗻𝗶𝘁𝘆𝗖𝗮𝗿𝗲 : A local community DApp where neighbors can communicate in real time, set up events, and receive notifications about local emergencies or activities. With conditional gating, special groups could be set up for neighborhood committees or watch groups. 𝟰. 𝗣𝘂𝘀𝗵𝗙𝗼𝗿𝗖𝗵𝗮𝗻𝗴𝗲 : A fundraising platform that sends out notifications about new charitable campaigns. Users can chat with charity organizers and use conditional gating to access exclusive fundraising events based on their donation history.
Qualification Requirements
"Namaste Push Protocol" seeks to acknowledge the innovative spirit of developers who merge social initiatives with technology. It's more than just a challenge; it's a call to action for developers to make a meaningful impact in the world using Push Protocol.
Resources
🤝Discord
https://discord.gg/pushprotocol
↗
Conditional Gating Group
https://push.org/docs/chat/build/conditional-rules-for-group/
↗
Notification/Channel settings
https://push.org/docs/notifications/build/create-channel-settings/
↗
Stream Notification
https://push.org/docs/notifications/build/stream-notifications/
↗
Push Documentation
https://push.org/docs/
↗
Hackers Guide
https://push.org/docs/hackers/

