About
Waku is a suite of robust communication protocols which can be used for private, censorship-resistant, scalable messaging.
With Waku you can send any kind of small payload in an off-chain and decentralized way, enabling 1:1, 1:1 and n:n types of communication.
Waku is powering the communication layer of the Logos network state technology stack. Logos is a grassroots movement to provide trust-minimised, corruption-resistant governing services and social institutions to peaceful people worldwide.
Prizes
▼
🏆 Best overall use of Waku ⸺ $4,000
This prize will be given to the most impressive project using Waku to solve a communication challenge
Qualification Requirements
Traditional chat-only applications will not be considered for the prize, although adding chat functions as a feature will not disqualify your project.
▼
🥷 Best privacy-focused project using Waku ⸺ $1,500
This prize will be given to the most impressive privacy-focused project using Waku to solve a communication challenge.
Qualification Requirements
Traditional chat-only applications will not be considered for the prize, although adding chat functions as a feature will not disqualify your project.
▼
🤝 Best game or marketplace using Waku ⸺ $1,500
This prize will be given to the most impressive game or a marketplace project using Waku to solve a communication challenge.
Qualification Requirements
Traditional chat-only applications will not be considered for the prize, although adding chat functions as a feature will not disqualify your project.
▼
🚀 Most innovative use of Waku ⸺ $1,500
This prize will be given to the most innovative use of Waku to solve a communication challenge.
Qualification Requirements
Traditional chat-only applications will not be considered for the prize, although adding chat functions as a feature will not disqualify your project.
▼
🗳️ Best network state goods using Waku ⸺ $1,500
Waku serves as the communications layer for the Logos technology stack. Bring us one step closer to building a network state by hacking a key communications solution using one of the Waku protocols.
Qualification Requirements
Traditional chat-only applications will not be considered for the prize, although adding chat functions as a feature will not disqualify your project.
Resources
Github
https://github.com/waku-org/
↗
Documentation
https://docs.waku.org/
↗
Projects built on Waku
https://github.com/waku-org/js-waku/network/dependents/
↗

