Fathom Protocol is an early-stage startup pioneering in decentralized finance (DeFi) on the XDC network. It aims to enhance liquidity through the over-collateralized stablecoin, FXD, to bridge DeFi with real-world assets. Fathom roadmap encompasses a broad spectrum, including Lending, DEX, DAO, and other products on the XDC network.
XDC, as an organization, is on a mission to improve the overall deficit in the global infrastructure with the help of Blockchain technology. XDC has revolutionized the concept of peer-to-peer transactions by using community-driven digital assets in an open-source blockchain platform.
The core idea behind our initiative is to make the transactions more secure and transparent among the parties involved in cross-border trade. XinFin, as an organization, believes in establishing an environment that will help businesses thrive without worrying about the hassles of international fund transfers.
Prizes
▼
🏆 Best Use or Extension of Fathom Protocol ⸺ $10,000

   ① $4,500       ② $3,500       ③ $2,000   
Ideas for Implementations:
- Enable private peer-to-peer transfers of Fathom FXD stablecoin using zero-knowledge proof technology.
- Develop Solidity smart contracts for stable pools like in Curve and integrate them with Fathom DEX.
- Create and integrate a Fathom DEX plugin that will allow cross-DEX swaps.
- Develop compliance features for FXD: daily limits, Know Your Customer (KYC) options, and wallet screening.
- Integrations for Fathom FXD stablecoin with DEXs/bridges/aggregators/etc.
- Integrations of Fathom Application with different open-source wallets.
The 1st place-winner team will have an opportunity for a Dubai trip where they will get a chance to visit the XDC Network Developer Center and have an amazing desert safari.
Qualification Requirements
As a result, we expect the working smart contracts (passing unit tests) and UI (huge bonus). Showcase the deployed dApp working on XDC mainnet / Apothem testnet.
Resources
XDC Website
https://xinfin.org/
↗
XDC Documentation
https://docs.xinfin.org/
↗
XDC Mainnet details
https://xinfin.network/
↗
XDC Testnet details
https://apothem.network/
↗
XDC Developer forum
https://www.xdc.dev/
↗
XDC Github
https://github.com/XinFinorg
↗
Fathom Website
https://fathom.fi
↗
Fathom Protocol Whitepaper
https://gist.github.com/BaldyAsh/3676a18b003758057f634c9af2cfe49a
↗
Fathom Github
https://github.com/Into-the-Fathom
↗
Fathom DApp
https://dapp.fathom.fi/
↗
FXD Mainnet Stablecoin
https://explorer.xinfin.network/tokens/xdc49d3f7543335cf38Fa10889CCFF10207e22110B5
↗
Fathom TypeScript SDK
https://www.npmjs.com/package/fathom-sdk
↗
Fathom Solidity SDK
https://github.com/Into-the-Fathom/fathom-solidity-sdk
↗
FXD Apothem Stablecoin
https://explorer.apothem.network/tokens/xdcDf29cB40Cb92a1b8E8337F542E3846E185DefF96
↗
Testnet Faucet
https://faucet.blocksscan.io/
↗
XDC Mainnet RPC list
https://chainlist.org/chain/50
↗
Apothem Testnet RPC list
https://chainlist.org/chain/51
↗
Fathom testnet app
https://demo.fathom.fi/
↗

