🛠️ XMTP + Airstack ⸺ $5,000

Up to 3 teams will receive $1,666
Create Onchain Friends SDK that enables any app to have users invite their friends (from onchain graph) to any app via XMTP invites - :fire: discuss with Airstack team; eligible for Airstack and XMTP bounties
Qualification Requirements
Create a working prototype app that allows users invite their friends (from onchain graph) to any app via XMTP invites
Resources
XMTP Developer Portal
https://xmtp.org/
↗
XMTP - Start Building
https://xmtp.org/docs/build/get-started/overview
↗

