About
ZetaChain is a layer 1 blockchain and developer platform that connects any L1 and L2, from Ethereum to Bitcoin and beyond. With ZetaChain you can build interoperable omnichain contracts or use cross-chain messaging between EVM chains.
Omnichain Smart Contracts are contracts deployed on ZetaChain that can use and orchestrate assets on connected chains, as well as on ZetaChain. With omnichain smart contracts you are able to have a single place of logic that can maintain the state of assets and data across all connected chains. You can implement cross-chain swaps, staking, lending protocols for Bitcoin or any cross-chain dapps.
Cross-chain messaging (CCM) lets you send messages from any connected chain to any connected chain, including ZetaChain. Cross-chain messaging makes the most sense for applications that generally need minimal logic or state to maintain across all chains, and where data that needs only to be passed between different chains one way.
Prizes
▼
🚀 Best Omnichain Contract ⸺ $2,000
ZetaChain is an EVM L1 that let's you build omnichain contracts. Users can deposit/withdraw value and call omnichain contracts from any connected chain. Create an awesome dapp that leverages ZetaChain's omnichain contracts capabilities.
Qualification Requirements
- Implement onCrossChainCall functionality
- Compatible with all chains connected to ZetaChain (Ethereum, Polygon, BSC, and Bitcoin)
- Use ZRC-20
- Implement custom logic (not tutorials or simple examples)
Links and Resources
Omnichain contracts overview
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/developers/omnichain/overview/
↗
Tutorials
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/developers/omnichain/tutorials/hello/
↗
Omnichain swap tutorial (video)
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t59EtsBequI
↗
▼
🟠 Best Contract for Bitcoin ⸺ $2,000
ZetaChain offers an EVM platform for developers to build contracts that can be deposited value and called from Bitcoin. Come up with and implement the most interesting use case for an omnichain contract compatible with Bitcoin.
Qualification Requirements
- Implement onCrossChainCall functionality
- Compatible with Bitcoin (compatibility with Ethereum, Polygon, and BSC is a plus)
- Provide useful functionality for Bitcoin users
- Let users deposit and withdraw BTC
- Use ZRC-20
- Implement custom logic (not tutorials or simple examples)
Links and Resources
Omnichain staking tutorial (compatible with Bitcoin)
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/developers/omnichain/tutorials/staking/
↗
Omnichain swap tutorial (compatible with Bitcoin)
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/developers/omnichain/tutorials/swap/
↗
Bitcoin frontend tutorial
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/developers/omnichain/tutorials/bitcoin-frontend/
↗
▼
✉️ Best Use of Cross-Chain Messaging ⸺ $1,000
ZetaChain offers general pupose cross-chain messaging (CCM) between connected EVM chains. Messages can transfer value and contain arbitrary data as payload. Find the most creative use-case for this technology.
Qualification Requirements
- Use ZetaChain's Connector API to send messages
- Implement onZetaMessage and onZetaRevert to handle messages
- Compatible with all connected chains (Ethereum, Polygon, BSC)
- Deploy to ZetaChain testnet
- Implement custom logic (not tutorials or simple examples)
Links and Resources
Cross-chain messaging overview
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/developers/cross-chain-messaging/overview/
↗
Introductory tutorial
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/developers/cross-chain-messaging/examples/hello-world/
↗
Resources
Documentation
https://www.zetachain.com/docs/
↗
GitHub
https://github.com/zeta-chain/
↗
Discord (#dev-general channel)
https://discord.gg/zetachain
↗

